Bartleby Montclair of Dresden everyone
across the land knows this name and they
should for he is the Emperor of the
Western Kingdom the most powerful
kingdom in the entire continent all
other kingdoms can only dream of being
as powerful and beautiful as it is
Bartleby is a beautiful man with golden
hair that flows in the wind and big-ass
and whistles in fact he is so beautiful
that some people who have never seen him
in person don't even believe he exists
but he does exist and he is sexy
legend has it that he has the power of
God No
beyond that that he is beyond even God
himself very few know however that this
is more than just legend this is fact
Bartleby's Sonic the Hedgehog
knows that it is fact because he's with
Bartleby every day of his life
he loves him with all his heart
Bartleby to love Sonic they love each
other so much that they would give the
world for each other they have but sex
almost every night chapter one today was
a very special day it was ample
harvesting day Apple harvesting day is
the one day of the year where Bartleby
ensoniq leave their empire and walk
across the last picking apples from high
up out of trees and handing the apples
out to poor people
since Bartleby is so rich he doesn't eat
apples only golden apples which bernal
begets from the mythical realm of
Valhalla which he bought two years ago
cause he's so rich however while
this is a joyous day for the people of
the western kingdom it is a very
dangerous day for the Emperor himself
Bartleby and his Sonic on Apple
harvesting day no one works so there are
no soldiers there to protect Bartleby
and Sonic while they out of the kingdom
this is especially dangerous for Sonic
who unlike Bartleby isn't strong enough
to protect himself should anything go
wrong but Sonic doesn't care as long as
he can be with his lover Bartleby that's
all that matters to him as Sonic and
borrowed by made their way down the
trail Bartleby groped Sonic's ass with
great force Sonic blushed at this and
blushed even harder when he looked over
and saw a bunch of kids pointing at
giggling at the couple Sonic took some
apples out of the basket they were
carrying ran over and gave the kids
apples and then something terrible
happened the kids tried taking more than
Sonic offered which was against the
rules of the kingdom so Sonic stabbed
one of the kids with his spear which
caused the rest of the kids to run away
screaming like little Sonic
called out to Bartleby with all his
lungs they're getting away Bartleby you
have to do something and Bartleby to do
something he pulled out a pistol and
popped a cap on each of their asses
after making sure each of them were dead
Bartleby and Sonic continued on their
way to hand out more apples to the
actual good villagers the ones who
deserved them chapter 2 as Bartleby and
Sonic walked down the trail they were
holding hands every now and then Sonic
would pick a flower from the ground and
give it to Bartleby where Bartleby would
proceed to put it in his flower basket
he had tied around his waist and was
hanging down near his sweaty butt crack
Sonic loved flowers Bartleby didn't care
for them too much but if his loved
him then well he loved them too of
course anything to make his happy
as they walked Sonic looked over and saw
the most beautiful flower he had ever
seen half of it was blue and half of it
was yellow almost as if it were a flower
that symbolized their love symbolized
Sonic immediately ran over and bent over
to pluck it from the ground as he was
bending over his ass was in full view
for Bartleby to see dear God did
Bartleby want to ravage that ass right
now and he was going to before he heard
a noise and then Sonic heard a noise
they looked to each other to make sure
they both heard it and then it happened
after three Sonic ran back over to the
trail and hugged Bartleby frightened
about what he heard he didn't know what
it was but it scared him they both
looked off to the north where they heard
the sound they heard it agent and again
Bartleby being the almighty being that
he was knew exactly what this was
footsteps and then on top of a hill
appeared a huge group of people all with
weapons
Bartleby knew right away who this was it
was the eastern kingdoms entire military
of over five million people all here to
try and kill Bartleby Sonic was so
scared he left on to Bartleby and cried
like a baby
Bartleby hugged back even harder to
comfort his lover and show him that
everything was going to be alright
suddenly all five billion pop we'll drew
their swords and began running down the
hill town roads and the two lovers the
people and back fired arrows they flew
through the sky
but since Bartleby was so fast he dodged
all the arrows with ease even catching a
few of them with his bare hands and
throwing them back at the people who
shot them in the first place
killing them instantly ten Bartleby
heard a scream he turned around and saw
that one arrow had pierced through
Sonic's arm it wasn't a fatal wound but
to someone not as strong as Bartleby it
must hurt like hell
Bartleby became furious he realized that
the eastern kingdom planned all of this
they knew Bartleby and Sonic would be
out of the castle today due to the apple
harvest and everything Bartleby looked
at his tears began to show in
Sonic's eyes and in that moment Bartleby
snapped chapter 4
can destroy Bartleby's kingdom you can
ruin apple harvesting day you can kill
his people but if you hurt Sonic dear
God if you hurt him you're going to be
dead
Bartleby ran over to a tree and ripped
the entire thing out of the ground the
people running down the hill all
suddenly stopped and once they realized
what they were getting into they all
turned and ran I the opposite direction
but it was too late they made their
choice by harming Bartleby's
Bartleby swung the tree back and forth
killing ten through twenty people with
each swing after the tree couldn't take
any more force Bartleby tossed it aside
and picked up another tree and used that
one instead and again and again after he
was all out of trees he pulled apples
out of his basket and threw them at
people with such force that it blew
their heads off and he threw one so
hard in fact that it went through 62
people before eventually disintegrating
from the friction at which Bartleby
threw it eventually they were all dead
all five billion of them afterwards
Bartleby went back over to make sure his
was all right and he was
thankfully when he saw Sonic he was
surrounded by family his siblings Sonya
and Manic does mom Queen Aleena and his
uncle Uncle Chuck they all made sure
Sonic was patched up enough so that him
and Bartleby could have sex at the end
of the day the end